Via de Carlo 20 Fontanelle, TV 31047 +39 327 9362164





eCRM Platform Operations Specialist | Front-end developer | SEO analyst



Creative technologist with advanced knowledge in Web front end languages and cross platform interactions.

- ★ I've earned more than 10 years of experience in End to End Web project management (conception / execution / operation / reporting / optimization) for local and multinational brands.
- ★ More than 5 years of experience working with remote, international, multidisciplinary teams at agency level.
- ★ Agile methodology proficient.

Experience



November 2022 - January 2023 Employer: Elita SRL Seasonal

Amazon Flex Driver



May 2017 - July 2019 Employer: Proximity Permanent contract

eCRM Platform Operations support analyst / Platform Operational Change Manager

May 2011 - December 2014

Technical support manager for Procter & Gamble's Golden Household eCRM platform / Title Digital media and social content planner



June 2020 - July 2022 Employer: Zoran Hub Own Business

Digital services manager, creative technician and cofounder of the Zoran Hub



August 2015 - November 2016 Company: Styling spaces / VIT

Styling Homes Agency Warehouse Logistic Operator / Search & Social digital campaign manager



June 2010 - April 2011 Company: Activamente

Digital Strategy Assistant / Multimedia producer



LEAD October 2008 - March 2010 Company: Lead2Action

Digital copywriter



Phone and address

Via de Carlo 20 Fontanelle, TV 31043 +39 327 9362164

Skills

Main

Agile end-to-end Web project management: Conception / execution / operations / reporting / optimization. SEO Webmastering: Creation of websites and networks with a scope of relevance to search engines.

Soft

Problem resolution in collaboration with remote teams.

Creative resourcefulness under pressure: Quick thinking and measured action during emergency situations.

Ability to summarize information in three Languages.

Artistic

Video production and edition: From the storyboard to the finalcut. Design: Manual (sketching) and digital (Photoshop / illustrator). Semantic: Good argumentation skills.

Programming languages and frameworks

HTML5 Advanced CSS3 Advanced JS Studying frameworks: angular, node, react, vue and jquery Bootstrap Intermediate Wordpress Advanced for website management / basic PHP

Digital marketing

Google myBusiness and Analytics management facebook and instagram organic page management Adwords and Social ads management

Languages

Spanish: Native. English: Bilingual. Italian: C2. French: Basic.

Education



Codecademy (e-learning) November 2019 - present **Web development (fullstack)**



Macquarie University (Sydney AU) 2006 - 2006 Master of arts in International Communications



lecnologico de Monterrey (MX) 2009 Marketing digitale (Certificate)



Universidad Iberoamericana (MX) 1999 - 2004

Bachelor in Communications